

RAKIBUR RAHMAN

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

An ambitious problem solver who is committed to developing skills with a passion for android applications. Experience in creating logical and innovative solutions to mobile application problems. I think and am precise in everything that I do, and have a keen interest in technology, mobile applications and user experience.

CONTACT

+8801736121557

Natun Bazar, Badda, Dhaka - 1229rakiburrahman.cse.eng@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/rakibur557

github.com/rakibur557

EDUCATION

Dhaka International University

BSc. in Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA - 3.92

2020 - Present (3rd year running)

SKILLS

Flutter

Dart, JSON, API, UML, XML, UI, Getx, Provider, Firebase, Animation, SQL(Basic), No-SQL, Git, SEO, Google Analytics.

LANGUAGE

Dart, JAVA, Node JS, Kotlin (Basic), Python,

C++, and C.

CERTIFICATE

Mobile Application and Games Development (Course)

Genex Info System Ltd.

Digital Marketing (Course)

TechBond IT Ltd

EXPERTISE

Management Skills
Leadership
Critical Thinking
Team Work
Hosting Events
English Language Proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

2021 - Present

Call Center Executive

Techbond IT Limited

DIU Computer & Programming Club

Treasurer

- Comes up with unique content for the members.
- Brainstorms innovative ideas for the club's portfolio.
- Works closely with the Research team.

2022 - Present

Hult Prize Organization

Campus Director (2022)

Media and outreach executive (2021)

2021 - Present

DIU CodeChef ChapterCompetitive Programming Lead

- Train the members about competitive programming.
- Support and manage problem-solving.
- Question setter to the contests.

2021 - 2022

BASIS Students Forum DIU Chapter
Executive Member

2022 - Present

Green School BD

Chief Executive Officer (CEO)

AWARDS

2022

BDApps National Hackathon - 2022

Team Edgefly - Winner (4th) in Dhaka & Mymenshing Regional Round and finalist.

NASA Space Apps Challenge -2021/22

Team Prehim Pro - Global Honorable Mention and winner in Barishal regional round (2022).

Team GreenX - Winner in Comilla regional round (2021).

O DIU CPC IT Carnival - 2021

Team Prehim - Winner at DIU CPC IT Carnival - 2021 in Project Showcasing.

2021 & 2022

2021020

2021